本片由 网址link3.cc/hirror 分享
- 老板.这是给你的.- 不,不,不.别这样.
- Boss. This for you. - No, no, no. Come on.
我不能占你们家便宜.
I can't impose on your family.
不要.
No.
雅斯敏特意为你做的.
Yasmin, she made this just for you.
老大,求你了.
Jefe, please.
拿着.
Take it.
替我谢谢她.
Tell her thank you.
好.
Yeah.
听着.
So, listen.
今天会很操蛋.
Today's gonna be hard.
全天都有检查.
We got inspections all day.
脚手架要拆还要搭
Forms to build, forms to break down
还有送货的来添乱.
and deliveries all gettin' in our way.
今天好好干,
We work hard today,
奖金少不了.
there'll be a bonus for ya.
明白?
Understand?
收工回家时
And let's all go home
都给我全须全尾地回家.
with the same amount of fingers that we came with.
行吧.
All right.
兄弟们.
Hermanos.
开工大吉.动起来.
Have a good day. Let's get it.
- 早啊,杰丝.- 早,莱文.
- Morning, Jess. - Buenos dias, Levon.
- 怎么样?- 挺好.
- How you doing? - I'm good.
- 谢啦.- 嘿,莱文.
- Gracias. - Hey, Levon.
今天没人找你借钱吧?
No one's been asking you for money today?
没.
No.
- 为啥?- 因为显然
- Why? - Because, apparently,
全家就我一个
I am the only person in the family
会做供应商账目.
who can do the vendor accounting.
哎哟喂!
Oh, excuse me!
看来咱俩是魔鬼家长啊亲爱的?
Hey, I guess we're evil parents, babe, huh?
让她干俩小时活就成恶人了.
'Cause we make her work a couple hours.
今天不行.
Not today.
先把付款单搞定行不?
How about you get those disbursements done, huh?
外头卡车排长龙等着结账呢.
We got a line of trucks out there that need paying.
你可以先结我的账.
You could pay me.
结你什么账?
Pay you for what?
十九年白吃白住,
For 19 years of free rent,
买菜钱,中学学费,
and groceries, and high school,
大学学费,化妆品,空手道班?
college, makeup, karate classes?
- 还要我继续报账吗？- 别,够了.
- You want me to keep goin'? - Really? No. It's okay.
莱文签个字行吗?
Levon, can you sign that, please?
- 爸?- 咋?
- Dad? - What?
- 今天简直鸡飞狗跳.- 我知道.
- Today is a total shitshow. - I know.
你还把三件事排同一时间.
And you scheduled three things at once.
她说得对.
She's not wrong.
喂,这里是加西亚家族建筑公司.
Hi, yeah. This is Garcia and Family Construction.
我是卡拉,
Yeah, you're speaking with Carla,
您让我等挺久了.
you've had me on hold for a bit now.
今天能按时送货对吧?
So, we're gettin' those deliveries today, right?
行 我继续等
Yeah, I'll hold.
这是我今晚需要的东西
This is what I need for tonight.
太离谱了吧 这什么玩意儿?这是要办婚礼还是咋的?
That's insane. What is that? Is that for your wedding or something?
不 是今晚用的
No, it's for tonight.
我们刚结束这学期 得庆祝一下
We finished the semester, so we're gonna celebrate.
要我说 这才刚读完一学期而已
I mean, you just finished one semester.
- 对啊 这可是人生里程碑 - 这也算?
- Right. It's a big milestone. - Is it?
- 当然算 - 真有这种说法?
- Yes. - Is that a thing?
听着 这已经算节制了好吗
Look, it could be worse, okay?
- 我这是在众筹呢 - 嗯嗯 对
- Look, I'm passing the hat. - Mm-hmm. Yeah.
- 够租辆派对巴士了 - 我的天
- That gets us a party van. - Oh, my God.
还能订个包间吃饭
Locks in a private room for dinner.
我最近省吃俭用
Just saving like crazy.
行 我需要登记信用卡信息
Yeah. I just need a card on file.
米娅,不行 我实在...
Mija, I can't. I don't...
米娅...
Mija...
好吧 算了 我不要了
Okay, fine. I don't need it.
她要什么就给她呗
Just give her what she wants.
不用 妈 我自己能解决
No, Mom, I can fight my own battles.
哎 没 没人说你不能
Oh, no, no, nobody's arguing that.
要我说 谁不需要个派对巴士呢?
I mean, everybody needs a party bus, right?
特别是刚读完一学期 拿去吧
After they finish one semester. Here.
谢谢
Thank you.
嘿 凯特
Hey, Kate.
打扰了
Excuse me.
他该回去干活了
He needs to get back to work.
给老子滚出去 少多管闲事
Get the fuck out of here. It's not your business.
我没事 老板
I'm good, boss.
都搞定了 五分钟就好
All good. Five minutes.
喂!
Hey!
等等 都把家伙放下
Hold on. Put down your weapons.
我可是很客气的
I was respectful.
你才没有
You weren't.
滚出去 起来
Get outta here. Get up.
别再来了
Don't come back.
-撤吧.-撤.
- Vamonos. - Vamonos.
没事吧?
You okay?
你怎么做到的?
How did you do that?
该回去干活了
We need to get back to work.
这个 搬到右边
This one. Over to the right.
- 明白 - 谢了凯特
- You got it. - Thanks, Kate.
莱文!我操!
Levon! Holy fuck!
刚才那是部队学的吧?
Was that some military shit?
刚才的事都给我烂在肚子里
You didn't see anything.
要是老爸知道 绝对气到原地爆炸
If Dad knew, he'd shit bricks.
能教我吗?
Can you teach me?
听着 我爷爷以前是伞兵
Look, my grandpa, he was a paratrooper.
教过我掰手指
Taught me how to break fingers,
追踪野兽
track animals.
掰手指?
Break fingers?
嗯
Yeah.
奶奶给你做了廷加鸡肉卷 手撕鸡那种
Grandma made you tinga. Shredded chicken.
超赞的
It's good.
奶奶还亲手给你揉了玉米饼
And Grandma made you some handmade grandma tortillas.
怎么个个都把我当猪养?
Why is everyone always feeding me?
不然你又要拿金枪鱼罐头配花生酱糊弄了
If we don't, you'll just eat canned tuna and peanut butter.
你什么都没看见 懂?
You didn't see anything, okay?
告密者缝嘴巴
Snitches get stitches.
哪天我要是栽了 记得捞我一把
Just get my back if I ever need it.
行行行 珍妮
Sure, Jenny.
走啦
See ya.
爱你哦老爸
Love you, Daddy.
我也爱你宝贝 快上车
Love you, too, honey. Get in the truck.
今天什么大日子?
What's the occasion?
没啥特别的
No occasion.
梅雷迪思要招待朋友
Meredith's entertaining some friends.
哦
Yeah.
我都忘了今天是你探视日
I didn't realize today was your visitation.
你本可以让她留下
You could let her stay.
就是啊罗特医生 没必要这么较真吧
Yeah, please, Doctor Roth, we don't have to do this.
她妈妈需要你时你不在
You weren't there when her mother needed you
梅雷迪思需要你时你也不会在
and you won't be there when Meredith needs you,
但我会
but I will.
呵 我懂
Oh, I know.
你想揍我对吧
You want to strike me.
这就是你唯一的答案
It's your only answer.
暴力倾向
Violence.
你是个不合格的家长
You're an unsafe parent.
你是个杀人犯
You're a killer.
别装得好像自己不是
You can't pretend that you're not.
打扰一下 罗斯医生
Excuse me, Doctor Roth.
今天是我的探视日
Today's my day.
为什么你爷爷要在我的探视日开派对?
Why's your grandfather throwing a party on my day?
我快饿死了 一直没吃东西
I'm super hungry. I didn't eat.
就等着和你一起吃
I was waiting for you.
真的吗?
You were?
嗯
Yeah.
好吧 我们走
Okay. Let's go.
- 你的餐齐了 - 谢谢
- Here you go. - Thank you.
- 请慢用 - 享用吧
- Thank you. - Enjoy.
你不用给我买东西的
I don't need you buying stuff.
快打开看看嘛
Come on. Open it.
是妈妈的照片
It's Mama.
这张照片是我拍的
I took that picture
用我爸送我的胶片相机
with a film camera my dad gave me.
爷爷把妈妈所有的照片都收起来了
Grandpa took all of Mama's pictures down.
有时候我都快记不清她的模样了
Sometimes I forget what she looks like.
她长得和你一模一样
She looks like you.
老爸,我能跟你说个事吗?
Dad, can I tell you something?
尽管说
Anything.
我气妈妈
I'm mad at Mama.
气她撒手人寰抛下我们
For dying and leaving us.
这很正常
It's okay.
我也很痛苦
I hurt, too.
马特现在要见你
Matt will see you now.
他故意在我探视时间给她办派对
He's throwing parties for her during my visitation time.
盯着我嘲笑
Staring at me, laughing.
他在故意激怒你
He's baiting you.
就盼着你挥拳头
Hoping you throw a punch.
不会的
Nah.
那样他就赢了
Then he wins.
对方律师
Opposing counsel
指控你有未治疗的创伤后应激障碍
alleges you have untreated PTSD
和服役期间造成的脑损伤
and brain trauma from your military service,
具有暴力倾向风险
making you at-risk for violence.
我为祖国英国效力了22年
I served Britain, the country of my birth, for 22 years.
他妈的反倒成恶人了?
I'm the fuckin' bad guy for it?
更糟的还在后头
It gets worse.
他们要求改为监督探视
They're requesting supervised visits
并将每周两小时的探视时间
and a reduction in visitation from two hours a week
缩短为每两周一小时
to one hour every two.
我必须反击
I have to fight this.
我存了一万英镑
I have ten grand saved up.
就靠睡你卡车后座攒的?
From sleeping in your truck?
法庭可不会买账
Court won't be thrilled
就因为你居无定所
by your lack of a fixed residence.
放心,我能搞定
Hey, I'll figure it out.
罗斯医生为什么这么恨你?
Why does Doctor Roth hate you so much?
他觉得我害死了他女儿
He thinks I killed his daughter.
真是你干的?
Did you?
她是自杀的
It was suicide.
当时我在海外执行任务
I was overseas on a deployment.
她这辈子都在和抑郁症抗争
She battled depression her whole life.
听说过消耗战吗?
You've heard of attrition warfare?
知道 就是慢慢拖垮敌人
Yeah. You grind the enemy down slowly.
对方有个律师天团
This guy's got a team
每小时收费上千美金
of thousand-dollar-an-hour attorneys
不榨干你最后一滴血
who will bleed you dry
直到你化为齑粉随风飘散
until you turn to dust and blow away.
咱们最多只能争取有条件投降
The best we can do is negotiated surrender.
你有女儿?
You have a daughter?
给姑娘们带了点小礼物
I got you guys a little somethin'.
妮娜
Nina.
乔丝琳...
Jocelyn...
- 尚特尔 还有露比 - 谢谢妈咪
- Chantel. And Rubi. - Thanks, Mama.
卧槽 这也太炸了吧!
Dude, these are insane!
哪儿搞来的?
Where'd you get these?
我有几个表亲 也就七八个吧
I have a cousin. Or seven.
姐妹们走一个!
Salud, bitches!
谢啦
Thank you.
举杯
Shots.
嘿!
Hey!
什么?怎么了?出啥事了?
What? What? What?
咱们还他妈杵在这儿干嘛?
What the fuck are we still doing here?
他说他要找真命天女
He said he wants the One.
"我要那个独一无二的 我他妈就要那个最特别的"
"I want the One. I want the fucking One."
这他妈到底几个意思?
What the fuck does that mean?
见到人他自然就明白了 懂?
He'll know it when he sees her, okay?
你知道这单能赚多少票子吗
Do you know how much fuckin' money
够咱们吃香喝辣一辈子
we're gonna make on this?
- 最好如此 - 玩得尽兴啊?
- We better. - Enjoy, yeah?
最后一家店了哥几个
Hey, last establishment.
你们不是要赶早班机吗
You guys have early flights.
那张靠后的桌子空着吗?
Is that back table open?
报上芳名就归你了
It's yours if you tell me your name.
我叫珍妮
It's Jenny.
你好 我是强尼
Hi, I'm Johnny.
你好呀 强尼
Hi, Johnny.
就坐这儿
Right here.
兄弟够意思
My man.
你比商业计划书重要多了
You are more than a pitch deck.
妮娜?
Nina?
- 妮娜 别吐啊 - 我没事
- Nina, don't throw up. - I'm fine.
她开始做呕吐表情了
She's making her puke face.
- 带她去洗手间 - 噫 好恶心
- Let's get you to a bathroom. - Oh, ew.
便宜货!晦气玩意
Cheap! Bad energy.
噫!
Ew!
我的天
Oh, my God.
我现在真想掐死你 一点也不好笑
I hate you so much right now, it's not funny.
其实还挺好笑的
It's kinda funny.
卧槽我这脸跟被雷劈过似的
Oh, my God, I look mad busted.
绝对不能让外人看见我这副鬼样子
I cannot go out there like this.
别折腾了 三十分钟后出发
Okay, well, pick your battles, 'cause we're leavin' in 30.
操!
Fuck!
快说
Go.
珍妮失踪了
Jenny's missing.
什么叫"失踪"?
What do you mean, "missing"?
周五她和朋友出去玩
She went out with her friends on Friday.
周六我们开始担心
Saturday, we were worried,
就报了警 结果周日...
so we called the cops, and then on Sunday...
周日晚她本来有钢琴演奏会
She had a piano recital on Sunday night.
我们邀请了半个家族的人
We invited half our family.
我表姐迪诺拉是费城警监
My cousin Dinora is a Police Captain in Philly,
她说条子压根不接这种案子
and she says they don't work these cases.
随便做个笔录就扔档案堆了
They take a report and forget about it.
你能帮我们吗?
Can you help us?
我可以维持工地正常运转
I can keep the site running smoothly.
不 帮我们找到珍妮
No. Help us find Jen.
我爸是绿色贝雷帽成员
My dad was a Green Beret.
你们这种套路我见多了
I can see you guys comin' a mile away.
你专门收拾恶棍
You hunt bad guys.
从万米高空玩跳伞
You jump outta planes.
把那些杂碎一网打尽
And you get those bad guys.
现在的我已经金盆洗手了
I'm a different person now.
好吧
All right, well,
或许这个能唤醒她
maybe this'll help her.
拿着 这是50块
Here, it's 50.
收下
Take it.
还有20块当活动经费
We have another 20 for expenses.
拿着吧老铁
Come on, just take it, man.
对不住了
I'm sorry.
那已经不是现在的我了
It's not who I am anymore.
枪叔 是我啊!
Gunny, it's me!
别开枪!
Don't kill me!
我带了牛排!
I got steaks!
刚才那一枪偏左一尺我就凉了
If you'd shot a foot to the left, I'd be dead.
想杀你早爆头了
If I wanted you dead, you'd be dead.
对我来说
You know, for me,
我的世界没有白天黑夜之分
there's no separation between day and night.
只能自己创造光明
So, I got to make my own.
活在灰色地带太煎熬
It's hard livin' in a gray world.
你的眼睛我没能保住
I couldn't save your eyes.
抱歉
Sorry.
这事让我寝食难安
That eats at me.
不
No.
你救了我的命
You saved my life.
要不是你当年捞我出来跑路
Joyce would be burying tags in the back yard
乔伊斯早该在后院给我立衣冠冢了
if you hadn't come along, scooped me up and ran.
那丫头叫啥名?
What's her name?
珍妮
Jenny.
珍妮 行
Jenny. All right.
是个乖孩子?
She a good kid?
绝世好闺女
She's a great kid.
听着 你要干这事就得豁出去
Now, you do this, you better lock in.
必须全力以赴 别留后手
You better go full on, no half-measures.
但只要你出手 那帮孙子就完了
But you do, God help 'em.
我答应过珍妮会罩着她
I told Jenny I had her back.
那个...
Well, uh...
挺想你的
I miss ya.
也担心你
I worry about ya,
但没必要特意跑过来假装请示
but you didn't have to come down here and pretend that
明明自己早就拿定主意了
you needed my permission for something
还整这出干啥
you already made your mind up about.
进来吧 开饭了
Get in here. We're eating.
卡拉
Hey, Carla.
谢谢你能来
Thanks for coming.
他人呢?
Where is he?
楼上 左手第一间
Upstairs. First door on your left.
"月光奏鸣曲"
"Moonlight Sonata".
- 嗯 - 真动听
- Yeah. - It's beautiful.
她当年可是拒了音乐学院的奖学金
She turned down a music scholarship
跑去读商学院
to go to business school.
一心想成为她老爸那样的人
She wanted to be like her pops.
当个地产大亨
Be a big land developer.
她肯定能成
And she will.
嗯
Yeah.
不用 谢了
Nah. No, thanks.
你家需要个盼头
Your family needs hope.
但我现在这德行没脸见她们
But I can't face 'em like this.
当年我老婆去世后
When my wife passed,
我从皇家海军陆战队退役
and I left the Royal Marines,
换别人早放弃我了
a lot of people would've given up on me.
但你们一直包容我
But you were patient with me.
-你 卡拉 珍妮 -珍妮
- You, Carla, Jenny. - Jenny.
你们就是我的家人
You're my family.
看着我 兄弟
Look at me, brother.
我绝对会带她回家
I'm gonna bring her home.
我发誓
I promise.
我铁定带她回家
I'm gonna bring her home.
"斯基普酒吧"
"Skip's Bar."
多谢款待 味道正吧兄弟?
Thank you very much. Good, bro?
还行不?嗯?
You good? Yeah?
感觉如何?
How you doing?
要不要整点前戏热热身?
You need a little aperitif, you know?
走着
All right.
哦豁,走错片场了吧靓仔？
Oh, yo. Wrong house, kid.
给老子圆润地滚犊子！
Get the fuck out.
强尼,搁这候着你呢.
Hello, Johnny.
要不要比划比划?看谁先嗝屁?
Wanna have a race? See who wins?
手给爷举高！起立！
Hands up. Stand up.
手插后脑勺唱《征服》那个姿势.
Place your fingers behind your head.
吃公家饭的?
You a cop?
条子能像老子这么温柔？
You wish I was a cop.
就懂你的那些猪朋狗友.
Your adventure, kid.
千金大小姐人呢?
Where's the girl?
哈？什么大小姐？
What girl?
布鲁克林区失踪三天的珍妮·怀特！
The missing girl.
你那帮兄弟从吧台后巷拖走的金主闺女！
The one your friends snatched outta the back of the bar.
条子早问过了,那小妞自己喝蒙圈跑路的.
I told the cops. She ran off. Drunk or somethin'.
废物点心两杯就找不着北,还装什么夜店咖？
Fuckin' poobutt can't hold her drink.
这锅也能往老子头上扣?
How's that my problem?
人类本质就是复读机+撒谎精.
People lie.
强尼啊...骗过我的人都在墳头蹦迪了.
Do you lie, Johnny?
人口贩子的嘴,骗人的鬼.
I don't trust people.
体液反应才是真·测谎仪.
I trust biology.
生物电流可不会演戏.
We're all wired the same.
三秒钟滚起来,别趴着装死狗！
Get the fuck up.
去你丫的！
Fuck you.
现在你脑子还知道泡的是浴缸
Your mind knows you're in the bathtub
蒙头的是浸水破布.
and it's just a wet towel.
但肾上腺素一上头,
But adrenaline makes your heart race,
肺泡都快被你吸爆炸.
so you burn more air.
身体可不管三七二十一,就觉得要变水鬼喽.
Your nervous system tells you that you're drowning.
泰姬陵会所知道你偷偷卖yao吗?
Your bosses know you deal dope over the bar top?
顺走收银机里的票子?
Steal from the till?
操你大爷!你他妈知道我是谁吗？
Fuck you!
那帮人可是职业撤漂的.
You know these guys are next level.
从太爷爷辈到曾孙子都得让你家族谱变空白！
They wipe out entire fucking bloodlines.
效率至上,懂.
Fair enough.
你我心里都门清,名单你是要吐出来的.
Just know you're giving me names.
文招武招随你选.
Your choice how.
强尼?
Johnny?
兄弟你人呢？兄弟？！
Where are you, brother?
搁这等外援呢?
You're expecting company?
操！老子等的就是他妈的特种部队！
Damn fuckin' right, I am.
给爷开门！今天不弄死你算我输！
Open the door. Fuckin' kill you.
俄国毛子！
Russians.
艹.
Fuck.
妈,孩儿不孝.
I'm sorry, Mom.
我对不起...
I'm sorry for...
这些年...
shielding myself...
被浮名虚衔裹成了木乃伊.
in a blanket of accomplishments.
真想让你看看...
I wish you could've seen me...
没戴人皮面具的我.
who I really am.
终其一生都在追逐你背影.
Just want to be strong like you.
我在这儿干吗?
What am I doing here?
扬声器模式老板,还是你自己看看吧.
on speaker It's better you see for yourself, boss.
没啥大不了的.
It's not a big problem.
你们两个他妈的到底干了什么?
What the fuck have you two done, huh?
他们为什么要互相开枪?
Why'd they shoot each other?
这他妈太不专业了.
This is very unprofessional.
强尼根本控制不住自己,他就是个怂货.
Johnny has no control. He's a weak man.
也许他开始胡吣,然后就到了「砰砰时间」.
Maybe he talk crazy, and then it's bang-bang time.
- 「砰砰时间」? - 对.
- "Bang-bang time"? - Yeah.
砰砰时间.
Bang-bang time.
你发现有什么不一样吗?
You notice anything different?
你的头发.
Your hair.
傻子.
Idiot.
我的钱呢?
Where is my fucking money?
你认为这是抢劫?
You think this was a robbery?
不可能.
Impossible.
没人会抢劫我们,没人那么傻,
No one would rob us. No one is that stupid,
或者那么疯.
or that crazy.
这是霰弹枪伤.
This is a shotgun wound.
你看到霰弹枪了吗?
You see any shotguns?
- 嗯? - 缺了九条.
- Hmm? - That's nine bands missing.
九万美元！我们的钱！
Ninety thousand dollars of our fucking money!
这是西蒙的钱.
It's Symon's money.
愿你的血净化这片土地,同志.
May your blood purify the soil, comrade.
嘿,亲爱的.
Hey, sweetheart.
嘿,爸爸,你在干吗?
Hey, Daddy, what are you doing?
嗯,没什么.只是,嗯……
Uh, nothin'. Just, uh...
只是一些工作.
Just some work.
- 你在上学吗? - 是的.
- Are you in school? - Yeah.
你应该从学校给我打电话.
You supposed to be calling me from school?
不.
No.
一切都好吗?
Everything okay?
是的,我只是想说「你好」.爸爸,我爱你.
Yeah, I just wanted to say, "hi." Love you, Daddy.
我也爱你.
Love you, too.
再见.
Bye.
这他妈的门自己开了?
The fucking door opens itself?
一切都他妈的完了!
Everything is fucked!
我不喜欢这样.
I don't like this.
我整晚一个人躺在床上.
I'm alone in the bed all night.
你吃了吗？
You eat.
你来床上躺一会儿.
You come to bed for a bit.
你以为钱是从天上掉下来的?
You think the money falls from the sky?
嗯?
Hmm?
糟糕透顶.
Bastard.
希望你不介意.
Hope you don't mind.
我饿了.
I was hungry.
想和你聊聊天.
Thought we could have a little chat.
我要把胶带撕掉.
I'm gonna take the tape off.
但如果你控制不住你的声音……
But if you can't control your volume...
你就去水里.
You go in the water.
你晓得老子是啥来头不?
Do you know who I am?
我需要知道吗?
Should I?
看来你根本不知道自己在撩哪根虎须.
You clearly have no idea who you fuck with.
来劲了？继续 看我口型说.
Make yourself happy. Tell me.
听说过咱们的万名册没?
You have heard of us?
如雷贯耳
I have.
哦豁?
Really?
战斗民族
The Vor.
铁血兄弟会 手足同心
The Bratva. The Brothers.
道上混的江湖人称盗贼联盟
The League of Thieves.
管你们俄罗斯老铁现在
Whatever Russian gangsters
换了多少茬名头装逼
like to call themselves these days.
看这架势您是个人物啊
You clearly are somebody.
敢动我们战斗民族的兄弟
You slaughter Vory soldiers.
还把我们的钱庄当提款机
You steal Vory money.
这波绝对是误会局
It was a misunderstanding.
老子可是堂口的扛旗长老
I am a brother of high rank.
从现在开始你这挂逼
You and all connected with you,
祖宗三代都得被我们全区追杀
will be hunted for three generations.
嗯哪 早就料到这出
Yep. I assumed so.
咱都知道道上规矩
We all know how these things play out
不把屁股擦干净就得凉
if you don't keep them tidy.
草泥马!
Fuck you!
这一拳是为你早上抽那姑娘的耳光
That's for slapping that woman this morning.
那姑娘是我媳妇儿
That woman was my wife.
这一巴掌是还你早上扇我老婆的.
That's for slapping your wife.
接着你的票子.
Here's your money.
老子不吃偷鸡摸狗这碗饭.
I'm not a thief.
你们道上的破事我懒得管.
I don't care about your business.
来找个表砸要人.
I'm lookin' for a young lady.
我... 我整不明白.
I... I don't understand.
就在你当黑窝使的那家酒吧地窖里,
The bar you do your dirty business out of,
有个19岁的小妹崽子被拐了.
a 19 year-old girl was kidnapped.
我今儿就是冲着她来的.
I'm lookin' for her.
迪米.
Dimi.
我劝你收收嗓门儿.
Maybe you should keep your voice down.
几个意思?
What do you want?
交出妞儿,
Gimme the girl,
大家井水不犯河水.
and everybody goes about their business.
就为个姑娘?
A girl?
整这么大阵仗就为个鸡?
All of this is for a girl?
黑道再脏也没听说为卖姑娘宰三条命的.
No one kills three people to sell a woman.
没人这么横.
No one.
老子不是人贩子.
I'm not selling her.
今天非把这姑娘全须全尾送回去.
I'm gonna bring her home.
天王老子也拦不住.
Not stopping until I do.
你混哪条道的?
Who are you?
到底什么来头?
What are you?
操你丫的.
Fuck you.
草!
Fuck you!
行了,我们结束了.
Okay, we're done.
迪米.
Dimi.
你他妈是谁,迪米?
Who are you, Dimi?
父亲.
Father.
他收钱.
He takes money.
他留了钱.
He leaves money.
他杀人从不手软.
He kills without fear.
问题是,为什么?
The question is why?
沃洛是个受人尊敬的爷们,
Wolo was a respected man of honor,
但他妈的儿子从来不像我们.
but his son was never like us.
迪米不是个生意人.
Dimi is not a businessman.
他更喜欢耍花枪,而不是老老实实干.
He prefers mischief over hard work.
他每天都在他妈的践踏他老子的心.
He spits on his father's heart every fucking day.
给我找到这孙子.
Find this man.
然后给我带回来.
And bring him to me.
我的名字是珍妮·加西亚.
My name is Jenny Garcia.
我的父亲是乔.
My father is Joe.
我的母亲是卡拉.
My mother is Carla.
你抓错人了,这是个误会.
You have the wrong girl. This is a mistake.
这他妈不是真的.
They're not real.
你他妈不是真的.
You're not real.
这...
This...
是操蛋的真的.
is fucking real.
吃你的操蛋东西,
Eat your fuckin' food,
然后你给我穿好那操蛋的衣服,
then you put on the fucking clothes
- 然后给我闭嘴! - 草!
- and shut the fuck up! - Fuck you!
你以前见过人死吗?
Have you ever seen someone die before?
嗯?
Huh?
他们的眼睛瞬间就蒙了.
Their eyes just cloud right over.
嗯,你他妈太漂亮了,对吧?
Mmm. You're so fuckin' pretty. Huh?
你不是吗,小公主?
Aren't you, Princess?
哦.
Aw.
啵.
Boop.
吃你的操蛋东西!
Eat your fuckin' food!
相信这个想法,
Believe the idea the
白袜队正在认真谈判
White Sox are in serious talks
在南环区建造一座新体育场,78号,
to build a new stadium in the South Loops, The 78,
芝加哥河旁罗素街附近的位置.
the location by the Chicago River just off Roosevelt.
我喜欢认真谈判
I love the idea of being in serious talks
在南环区建造一座新体育场的想法.
for a new stadium in the South Loop.
最近怎么样,老兄?靠承包发财了吗?
How's it goin', cat? Getting rich contracting?
哦,是的.更像在浇混凝土.
Oh, yeah. Pouring concrete more like.
我退出了这行.现在是个老实的纳税人.
I'm outta the game. I'm an honest taxpayer now.
你和枪叔谈过吗?他怎么样?
You talked to Gunny? How's he doing?
前几天见过他.他很快乐.
Saw him the other day. He's happy.
说吧,你从不主动给我打电话,除非你需要什么,
Well, you never call me unless you need something,
所以,你想要什么?
so, what do you want?
在找一个叫迪米的孙子.
Lookin' for someone called Dimi.
可能是德米特里.沃尔奥德米尔·科利斯尼科的同伙.
Probably Dimitri. An associate of Wolodymyr Kolisnyk.
那是个大人物,老兄.
That's a high-ranking dude, cat.
黑手党的头头.
Mafia captain.
正牌的「布拉特瓦」操盘手.
Legit Bratva shot caller.
不是你想惹的人.
Not a guy you wanna fuck with.
从来不会.
Nah, never.
这个叫迪米的主儿,
This Dimi fella,
他可能在搞人口走私.
he might be involved in human trafficking.
你能查一下NADDIS和NCIC吗?看看有没有线索?
Can you check NADDIS and NCIC? See if you can get a hit?
我得小心,
I gotta be careful,
但在Joliet有一家叫Hattie's的酒吧,
but there's a bar called Hattie's in Joliet,
他们在那里给俄罗斯人卖毒品.
where they sell meth for the Russians.
或许你应该去那儿喝一杯.
Maybe you should get a beer there.
不错.谢谢.
Nice one. Thanks.
嘿.喝点什么?
Hey. Whatcha havin'?
我就喝啤酒.你随便挑.
I'll just have a beer. You pick.
行.
Okay.
哦,嘿,陌生人.你去哪儿了?
Oh, hey, stranger. Where you been?
就是想赚点钱.
Tryin' to make a buck.
你知道,
You know,
有传言说你和你那个垃圾兄弟
rumor has it you and your shitbag brother
在和俄罗斯人打交道.
have been talkin' to the Russians.
有传言说你当时太嗨了,
Rumor has it you were so high,
在一个陷阱屋里不小心杀了大迈克,
you accidentally killed Big Mike in a trap house
然后把责任推到一个抢劫团伙身上.
and blamed it on a robbery crew.
去他妈的.去他妈的...
Fuckin' shut up. Fuckin'...
要是达奇发现有人绕过他跟毛子搭线
Dutch finds out anybody's talkin' to the Russians but him,
这老哥绝对要原地爆炸
he's gonna lose his fuckin' mind.
嘘!
Shh!
认识这货吗?
Do you know this guy?
不认识 头回见
No. I've never seen him.
看着不顺眼
I don't like him.
条子相
Looks like a cop.
裤兜里揣着家伙
He's got a gun in his pocket.
像是点三八 瞅见没?
Like a .38. You see it?
操 看见了
Fuck. Yes.
该你上了 菜鸟
You're up, kid.
跟我来
Follow me.
去跟人搭话
Go talk to the man.
找乐子呢?
You lookin' for somethin'?
兄弟我只对药房生意感兴趣
My interests are strictly pharmaceutical, brother.
老铁带家伙几个意思?
Any reason why you packin' heat, brah?
身上揣着现金
I'm carrying money.
防着点拿刀劫道的
Hate to lose it to a man with a knife.
他是条子
He's a cop.
你是警察吗?
Are you a cop?
不是啊 你是?
Nah. Are you?
掏兜吧 条子
Run your pockets, Chief.
咱们查查警徽在不在
Let's check for that badge.
听见没
You heard the man.
把东西摆桌上
Put it on the table.
现在.
Fuckin' now.
我来这里不是为了受辱的.
I didn't come here to be disrespected.
好吧.
All right.
让我们开始.
Let's play.
抓住他.
Get him.
抓住他,兄弟.
Get him, brother.
再见,混蛋.
Bye, asshole.
够了!
Enough!
我爷爷告诉我,坐着的时候不要和人握手.
My grandpa told me to never shake hands sittin'.
看看那些砖头.
Look at those bricks.
你不是警察,你是干活的.
You ain't a cop, you're a working man.
我这辈子都在搞建筑.
Been in construction my whole life.
你当过兵吗?
Were you a soldier?
因为你打架像一个士兵.
'Cause you fight like a soldier.
我尽力了.
I did my part.
我是空降兵.
I was Airborne.
他们训练我们从飞机上跳下来,
They trained us to jump outta planes
结果我们最后坐着公交车去打仗.
and we ended up ridin' a bus into combat.
听起来差不多.
Sounds about right.
坐下吧,兄弟.
Have a seat, brother.
我听说你有购买意向.
I heard you're in a buyin' mood.
我在找蓝色玻璃,
I'm lookin' for blue glass,
好货.
the good stuff.
我需要重量.普通的.
I need weight. Regular.
比如一个月四磅.
Like four pounds a month.
就这?
That's all?
你倒手卖给谁?
Who you flippin' it to?
该去哪就去哪
It goes where it's needed.
客户是我的事 你少操心
The customers are my concern, not yours.
为啥选这儿?为啥找我们?
And why here? Why us?
芝加哥的接头人失联了
My Chicago connect is missin' in action.
我手下施工队全天三班倒连轴转
I'm runnin' work crews in shifts 24/7.
时间就是金钱
Time is money.
半磅七千刀
Seven K for half a pound.
这可是芝加哥行情价
That's a Chicago price.
五千
Five.
往北直走高速路口
There's a pancake house
有家松饼屋
at the highway junction straight north of here.
七点整 过来吃早饭
Be there, 7:00 a.m., having breakfast.
然后呢?
And?
带上五千现金
And bring five stacks.
聊得愉快
Good talk.
现在赶紧给老子滚
Now get the fuck outta here.
坐吧
Have a seat.
嗯
Mm.
这整得跟大型社死现场似的
This is like an awkward Tinder date.
直接把钱给她得了
Just give her the money.
呵 果然不出所料
Mmm. Lo, and behold.
人言可畏
People talk,
有钱能使鬼推磨
money fucks.
你有什么东西要给爷吗?
You got somethin' for me?
我们他妈根本就不知道你是谁,兄弟.
We don't know who the fuck you are, brother.
你会接到一个电话,告诉你你的破玩意儿在哪里.
You'll get a call tellin' you where your shit is.
就这?
That's it?
是的.嗯,是的.
Yeah. Uh-huh.
别耍爷.
Don't play me.
爷知道怎么找到你.
I know where to find you.
是的.我想是的.
Yeah. I guess you do.
感谢你没把爷崩了.
Thank you for not shooting me.
操蛋玩意儿.
fuckin' asshole.
- 是吗? - 好吧,你准备好了吗?
- Yeah? - All right. You ready?
爷要告诉你「skante」在哪里,大狗.
I'm gonna tell you where the skante's at, big dog.
爷在等.
I'm waitin'.
在你座位下面.
Under your seat.
- 谢谢. - 留着这个烧号手机.
- Thank you. - Keep the burner phone.
爷明天会联系你.
I'mma hit you tomorrow.
然后你可以告诉我你们这些混蛋是如何在我的地盘上一天就建起罗马的.
Then you can tell me how y'all motherfuckers
在一天内建起罗马的破玩意儿.
built Rome in a day off my shit.
然后我们可以谈谈重量.
Then we can talk about weight.
猜猜谁今晚要当公主?
Guess who's gonna be princess for a night?
你是迪米的奇迹制造者,对吧?
You are Dimi's miracle workers. Huh?
而且,这是给迪米的奇迹.
And that, that is for Dimi's miracle.
为什么是她?
Why her?
她让我想起了我父亲房子里的一幅画.
She reminded me of a painting in one of my father's houses.
把她带到后面.
Take her in the back.
好
Sure.
看这些小可爱多萌
Look how cute these ones are.
像小鲨鱼似的
They look like little sharks.
跟你一样可爱呢宝贝
Just like you, cutie.
她咬我!
She bit me!
她不是该在睡觉吗!
She's supposed to be asleep!
实在对不起先生
I'm so sorry, sir.
给我把她弄走!
I want her out!
嗯?
Yeah?
他们喜欢我的货吗?
Did they like my shit?
只能说他们很满意
Let's just say they were pleased.
这样的货要多少有多少
There's plenty more where that came from,
但咱们要合作的话
but there's someone you gotta check in with
你得先跟个人打招呼
if we're gonna do business.
什么意思?
What does that mean?
预防措施嘛兄弟
Precautionary measures, brah.
毕竟联邦政府现在可是按磅量刑
Seein' as the Feds are handin' out life sentences per pound.
这行当可不是谁都能干的
Yeah, this game's not for everyone.
明白老哥
I hear you, big dog.
我会约个时间面谈
I'mma shoot you an invite for a sit-down.
带够现金穿正装来
Bring your money and wear a suit.
我没正装
I don't have a suit.
操 明天就有了
Shit. You will tomorrow.
因为要见的是最顶层的大佬
'Cause these motherfuckers are as high power as it gets.
我来找叫达奇的人
I'm here to see someone called Dutch.
这边请
He's right this way.
人在那边
He's over there.
- 最近怎样?- 嘿达奇
- How you doin'? - Hey, Dutch.
钱带了吗?
You bring the money?
可以吗?
May I?
先把手机给我关机
First, you gotta turn your phone off.
现在呢?
Now what?
钱已经在你手上了
You already have my money.
我可是诚心诚意来谈生意的
I came here in good faith to do business.
我叫迪米
My name is Dimi.
你呢?
Yours?
比尔
Bill.
比尔·科茨
Bill Coates.
有驾照吗比尔·科茨?
Do you have driver's license, Bill Coates?
什么意思?
Excuse me?
没事 让他查
It's fine. Let him check.
你开的是租来的车
You drive rental.
我们查了车牌
We check plates.
抵税用的
Tax write-off.
有问题吗?
That okay?
这位是我生意伙伴
This man is my business partner.
他是小角色
He is small potatoes.
我才是话事人
I am the big potatoes.
直说吧
Tell me.
你会不会给我找麻烦?
Will you be a problem?
这就是你们做生意的方式?
Is this how you do business?
你把我叫到这里来威胁我?
You invite me here to be threatened?
没问题.
Checks out.
我为此向你道歉,「威廉」.
I apologize for that, "William."
你显然是一个……
You are clearly a...
严肃的人.
serious person.
如果你需要补给,使用烧号.
If you need resupply, use the burner.
发送兔子 emoji.
Text bunny rabbit emoji.
兔子 emoji.
Bunny rabbit emoji.
你知道我需要每月四磅?
You made aware I need four pounds a month?
哦.
Oh.
然后发送茄子 emoji.
Then text eggplant emoji.
我们知道了.
We are aware.
如果你喜欢盒子里的东西,
If you like what is in the case,
我们可以做更多生意.
we do more business.
现在,你离开,别回头看.
Now, you leave and don't look back.
对我来说没问题.
Fine by me.
强尼,你真是个烂透了的家伙.
Johnny, you're a real piece of shit.
你这个狡猾的混蛋.
You sneaky motherfucker.
嗨,操蛋玩意儿.
Hi, asshole.
嗯.
Hmm.
他在这里.
He's here.
- 哦,shit. - 在扬声器上 他开着一辆黑色的道奇公羊
- Oh, shit. - on speakers He's in a black Dodge Ram
藏在树后面.
hiding in the trees.
好的,我们现在过去.
Okay, we're pulling up now.
上!
Let's go!
操!他他妈骑摩托跑了!追!
Fuck! He just fuckin' left on a bike! Go!
快追!快追!快追!
Go! Go! Go!
妈的!
Fuck!
把手举起来.
Show me your hands.
嘿.
Hey.
你们没看见我们在这儿.
You didn't see us here.
啥他妈都没发生.
Nothing fucking happened.
这里交给我们处理.
We'll take it from here.
你也是被收买的?
You're on the payroll too?
你怎么认识迪米的?
How do you know Dimi?
你和迪米有什么勾当?
What is your business with Dimi?
啊,你们两个混蛋.
Ah, you two assholes.
那个被你淹死的男人,
That man you drowned,
在他老婆练普拉提的时候,在自家泳池里,
in his own pool while his wife was at Pilates,
那是我们舅舅.
that man was our uncle.
他嘴巴太碎了.
He wouldn't shut up.
我警告过他.
I warned him.
- 知道我们是谁吗？嗯？- 喂！喂！
- Do you know who we are, hmm? - Hey. Hey.
知道啊,穿老妈挑的土鳖衣服那帮人呗.
Yeah, people whose ma dresses 'em funny.
这他妈是高定懂不懂！
This is fucking couture, man.
这是我们的品牌风格!
It's our fucking brand!
把他腿绑上.
Tie up his legs.
想吓唬我？你们得再加把劲.
If you want me to be scared, you gotta try harder.
卧槽!
Whoa!
宰了这恶魔
Kill this demon.
这是万科
That is Vanko.
那是丹雅
And that is Danya.
这都是我儿子
These are my sons.
我的家族血脉
My house and my lineage end
就要断送在这冰冷铁床上了
on these cold, steel tables.
召开战事会议
Convene the war counsel.
借过 亲爱的
Excuse me, dear.
滚犊子
Fuck off.
哇哦
Oh, wow.
绝对他妈不行
Absolutely fuckin' not.
操
Oh, fuck.
你能活着就该烧高香了
You're lucky you're not already dead.
迪米 我道歉行了吧?
Dimi, apologies, okay?
对不起 真心诚意地道歉
I'm sorry. I'm truly fuckin' sorry.
她咬掉了他半张脸
She fucking bit half his face off.
- 严格来说没到半张脸 不过... - 哦
- It wasn't exactly half his face. But... - Oh.
缝了三十六针
Thirty-six stitches.
真不少
That's a lot.
才把腮帮子缝回去
To reattach his cheek.
老子做的是快活生意 不是外科手术
I am in the business of pleasure, not surgery.
告诉我...
Tell me...
操
Fuck.
你懂什么叫生意吗?
Do you know what business means?
我...不 我是说 懂 妈的
Do I... No. I mean, yeah. Fuck.
生意就是
Business means
要讲信用
you keep your word.
兑现承诺 让客户满意
You deliver promises. You make customer happy.
不是他妈咬人脸!
Not bite fucking face off!
- 明白了 - 不
- Understood. - No.
你害老子亏了二十万美刀
You just fucked me out of 200 grand.
你赚一份 我抽两份
If you make one, I make two.
客户要她死 我也要她死
Customer wants her dead. I want her dead.
你杀了她 知道往哪送
You kill her. You know where to take her.
包您满意
Consider it done.
现在滚蛋!
Now fuck off!
这就滚 老大
Fucking off, sir.
我操他气炸了
Holy shit, he was pissed.
何止生气 差点就把咱俩都崩了
Fucking beyond. He was this close to smokin' us both.
得做了那妞
We gotta whack that girl.
我没意见 干死那小婊子
Fine by me. Let's do the little bitch.
我们面对的是个魔鬼
We are facing a devil.
这魔鬼杀了我两个手下
This devil kills two soldiers.
淹死了沃洛迪米尔
He drowns Wolodymyr,
那可是位德高望重的船长
an esteemed captain.
现在又杀我儿子
Now he kills my sons.
你该明白我的担忧吧?
You do understand my concern?
迪米在哪?
Where is Dimi?
他不该知道这魔鬼是谁吗?
Won't he know who this devil is?
迪米在躲猫猫
Dimi's hiding.
他们会帮你找到迪米
They will help you find Dimi.
感谢你告知此事
Thank you for bringing this to my attention.
现在出发
Now go.
来点香槟?
Some champagne?
你爹已经死了
Your father is dead.
被绑在椅子上
Tied to a chair
溺死在自己泳池里
and drowned in his pool.
所以这算好消息？
So, it's good news.
杀他的那个人
The man who killed him
也宰了我两个儿子
murdered my sons.
丹雅和万科?
Danya and Vanko?
操！
What the fuck?
你居然不知道?
You did not know this?
我他妈怎么会知道?根本没人告诉我！
How the fuck would I know? Nobody tells me anything.
兄弟会把我当瘟神躲着
The Brotherhood treats me like I'm radioactive.
这人到底是谁?
Who is this man?
我好声好气问你
I ask with kindness.
我资助飞车党搞冰毒生意
I bankroll biker gang with meth connection.
他们介绍了个现金买家
They introduce me to buyer with real cash.
就碰面五分钟
We met for five minutes.
仅此而已
That's it.
等等 等等等等
Wait. Wait, wait, wait.
我有线索
I have this.
他在追杀你
He's hunting you.
找到他了
Found him.
哦
Oh.
- 喂?- 你好 凯德先生?
- Hello? - Hi. Mr. Cade?
这里是总务处
This is the Main Office.
呃 今天没人来接梅雷迪思
Um, no one's come to pick up Meredith today.
我马上到
I'll be right there.
- 嘿 - 今天顺利吗?
- Hey. - Good day?
- 嗯 - 走吧
- Yeah. - Let's go.
爷爷人呢?他从来不会迟到
Where's Grandpa? He's never late.
电话也不接
He's not answering me.
我给他发了得有二十条消息
I sent him, like, 20 messages.
肯定没事的
I'm sure he's fine.
你没把老爷子给做了吧?
You didn't kill him, did you?
爸 我开玩笑的
Dad, I'm kidding.
你信得过我吗?
Do you trust me?
当然
Yeah.
所以如果我告诉你什么事
So, if I tell you something,
你知道可以相信我 对吧?
you know you can believe me, right?
好吧 铺垫只会让事情更糟
Okay, the build-up is just making it worse.
我捅大篓子了
I made a big mistake.
天呐 你真把爷爷杀了？
Oh, my God. You did kill Grandpa.
梅丽 我是认真的
Merry, I'm serious.
有帮狠角色在追杀我
Some really bad people are after me,
我不想让爱的人受牵连
and I don't want anyone I love to get hurt.
你跟爷爷共享位置了吗?
Are you sharing your location with Grandpa?
嗯
Yeah.
能看到他的定位吗?
Can you see his location?
可能吧 不确定
Maybe, I don't know.
爸爸 他在家里
Daddy, he's at home.
梅丽 待在这儿别动
Merry, stay here, okay?
梅丽!待在原地!
Merry! Stay there!
爸爸小心!
Daddy, be careful!
那些是什么人?
Who were they?
俄罗斯黑手党?
Russian mafia?
对
Yes.
他们是冲你来的
They were looking for you.
这都是你惹的祸
This happened because of you.
暴力就像乌云一样跟着你
Violence follows you like a cloud.
爷爷 他本可以把你留在火场里
He could've left you in there, Grandpa.
但他救了你的命
He saved your life.
这点我承认
I can acknowledge that.
你该去医院
You should go to the hospital.
那里比较安全
You'll be safe there.
我来照顾梅丽
I'll take care of Merry.
该让警察处理了
It's time o let the cops handle this.
警察拦不住他们
Cops can't stop them.
好吧
All right.
晚点再想办法
We'll figure it out later.
还有 莱文
And, Levon,
谢谢你
thank you.
还记得枪叔吗?
You remember Gunny?
你那个不知道自己失明的盲人朋友?
Your blind friend who doesn't know he's blind?
就是他
That's the one.
他在乡下有栋房子
He has a country house.
暴风雨过去前我们待那儿安全
We'll be safe there till the storm passes.
嗨
Hi.
要进来吗?快进来
You wanna come inside? Come on.
- 饿吗?- 永远饿
- You hungry? - Always.
- 你呢?- 嗯
- And you? - Yeah.
老兄 发生什么事了?
What happened, man?
你惹错人了吧?
You fuck with the wrong people, huh?
嘿 你本可以阻止我的
Hey, you could've stopped me.
这世上有什么能拦住你?
What force on earth is gonna stop you?
情况越来越糟了
It's gettin' ugly.
你真能找到那姑娘?确定能找到吗?
Can you find this girl? Can you really find this girl?
我能找到她
I can find her.
我会带她回家
I'm gonna bring her home.
这话中听 有计划吗?
I hear that. You got a plan?
我要去问那个叫迪米的家伙
I'm gonna ask this Dimi fella where she is.
所有线索都指向他
All roads lead to him.
既然你是杀进来的
Now, you killed your way into this,
就得杀出去
you're gonna have to kill your way out of it.
我猜也是
I figured as much.
这方面我能帮你
I can help you with that.
哦是吗?
Oh, yeah?
给你看个东西
Let me show you somethin'.
您先请 先生
After you, sir.
好吧 今晚就由我担任您的军械侍酒师
All right, I will be your weapons sommelier
为您挑选趁手兵器
for this evening.
绕过这面墙
If you come around this wall,
您会看到这把AK自动步枪
you see the Avtomat Kalashnikov,
从1947年就开始收割美国大兵
been killing Americans since 1947.
这里还有豪华镶钻版
Also, comes in a deluxe, blingy version pulled direct
直接从萨达姆行宫顺来的
from Saddam's palace.
这边是M4卡宾枪
What you got over here is the M-Four Carbine,
堪称反恐战场的五菱宏光
it's the Chevy Impala of the war on terror.
这把MP5 SD消音冲锋枪适合暗杀
Beautiful MP5 SD here if you wanna kill somebody,
保证目标在睡梦中安详去世
but you don't wanna wake 'em up.
但真正的狠角色在这儿
But this is the real beast here.
这可是天启四骑士的原始装备之一
One of the original weapons of
地狱使者的标配武器
the four horsemen of the apocalypse.
M14狙击步枪
The M14.
您应该记得这把枪吧
You might remember this weapon.
我宁愿忘记 但确实记得
I don't want to, but I do.
拿好
There you go.
我得磨掉枪号
I'll have to drill out the serial numbers.
不用 早就处理过了
Oh, no, that's already done.
这些武器从未存在过 就像我们当年
These were never here. Never anywhere.
就像我们一样
Kinda like us,
来无影去无踪
back in the day.
咱们当年干的可是替天行道的好事 兄弟
We did some righteous shit, brother.
确实如此
Yeah, we did.
- 那里面是什么?- 少打听
- What's in there? - None of your business.
我能一起去吗?
Can I come?
绝对不行
Absolutely not.
那学校怎么办?
What about school?
最多缺几天课
You'll miss a couple of days, at most.
我几乎见不到你
I barely see you.
我不想你惹上麻烦
I don't want you getting in trouble.
那样我就永远见不到你了
Then I'll never see you.
不会的
That's not gonna happen.
看这个?这是你
See this? This is you.
各占一半
Half and half.
我要你保管好这个
I want you to hold onto this.
我会回来取的
I'm comin' back for that.
好
Okay.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你 爸爸
Love you, Daddy.
爸爸 我不想你受伤
Daddy, I don't want you getting hurt.
我很快就回来 好吗?
I'll be back soon, okay?
枪叔 照顾好她
Gunny, take good care of her.
当然
Yeah, of course.
- 谢谢你 乔伊斯 - 这边走
- Thank you, Joyce. - This way.
- 再见 莱文 - 保重 甜心
- Bye, Levon. - All right, sweetheart.
"我们在天上的父
"Our Father,
愿人都尊你的名为圣
who art in heaven,
愿尔名见圣,
hallowed be thy name,
愿尔国降临,
thy kingdom come,
愿尔旨得成."
thy will be done."
上帝不在这儿,小甜心.
God ain't here, sweetheart.
睡得好吗小公主?
Have a nice nap, Princess?
得靠边给这贱货
We gotta pull over and load this bitch
灌点安眠药...
with some fuckin' sleeping pills...
卧槽卧槽卧槽!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- 臭婊子! - 嘿,冷静点!
- Fucking bitch! - Hey, take it easy!
- 停车! - 快!停下!
- Pull over! - Come on! Stop!
抓住她,这该死的贱人！
Fucking get it, fucking bitch.
快逮住那个臭娘们!
Fucking grab that bitch!
靠边!停车!熄火!
Pull over! Pull over! Pull over!
妈的!老子的枪呢!
God damn it! Where's my fucking gun!
操!
Fuck!
淦.
Fuck.
快他妈动啊毒蛇!
Fuckin' move, Viper!
草!日!
Fuck! Fuck!
不是,这他妈什么情况?
I mean, what the fuck?
这娘们车技真溜.
She is fast.
咱们要二进宫吃牢饭了!
We're going back to fuckin' prison!
哈?
Huh?
嗯?听明白没?
Huh? You get it?
懂,我懂,都懂.
Yeah, I get it. I get it.
艹!行行行.
Fuck! Okay, okay.
操!操!
Fuck! Fuck!
妈的.
Shit.
行啊大聪明
Okay, genius,
现在咋整?
now what?
你没事吧?
Are you all right?
我叫珍妮·加西亚,被绑架了
My name is Jenny Garcia. I was kidnapped.
没事了 我们知道你是谁
It's all right. We know who you are.
带你回家
Let's get you home.
好
Okay.
我他妈真的对不起
I'm so fucking sorry.
想我了吗?
Miss me?
操!
Fuck!
爆了这婊子的头!
Fucking dome the bitch!
- 你他妈在逗我？- 是他吗？
- You gotta be kidding me. - Is that him?
这他妈什么情况?
What the fuck?
操！是视频通话
Fuck, it's a video call.
接着！拿好这破手机！给我那......
Here, take the fucking phone! Give me the...
- 操!- ......他妈的破枪
- Fuck! - ...God damn fucking gun.
嘿老大
Hey, sir.
迪米说你们还扣着那女孩
Dimi says you still have the girl.
呃 是是 人还在
Uh, yeah, yeah. We still got her.
让我看看她还活着
Show me she's still alive.
看见没?活蹦乱跳
See? Still alive.
今晚农庄二番战
I want a second date tonight, at the farmhouse.
一百万美元
One million dollars.
呃,好的.您想怎样都行,老板.
Uh, yeah. Whatever you want, sir.
我这就给她梳洗打扮,保证浑身香喷喷.
I'll get her cleaned up and smelling real pretty for you.
不,不,我要她脏兮兮的.
No, no, no. I want her dirty.
不要昏昏欲睡,
Not sleepy,
要脏兮兮但活蹦乱跳.
but dirty and alive.
暂时先这样.
For now.
- 操,没问题.- 哦,好的.
- Fuck, yeah. - Oh, yes.
用哪本护照？红色？蓝色？绿色？
Which passport, okay?
你他妈给我这么多本护照.
You sent me all these passports.
我分不清啊！红色?蓝色?绿色?
I can't tell. Red? Blue? Green?
- 我哪知道颜色,快说！- 咱们要去哪?
- I don't know what color, just tell me. - Where are we going?
什么?行吧.赶紧走.
What? Okay. Yeah. Go.
我全带上总行了吧?
I take all of them, okay?
- 你想要什么?要钱?- 不,我不要...
-What do you want? You want money? -No, I don't...
拿着你的臭钱！都给你！
Here, take your money. You take money.
老子不稀罕你的臭钱!
I don't want your fucking money!
- 钱都归你.- 我不要
- You take all the money. - I don't want
- 你的脏钱!- 钱全归你,行了吧?
- your fucking money! - You take all the money, okay?
- 让我帮你!- 不用,我不需要帮忙.
- Let me help you! - No, no, I don't need help.
操.
Fuck.
滚开!别过来!
Get away! Stop!
从明天开始戒毒.
Starting tomorrow, rehab.
你只会看着我堕落.
All you do is let me slip down slippery slope.
你本该是我的靠山.
You're supposed to be my rock.
就像人们常说的"她是我依靠".
You know, like they say, "Oh, she's my rock."
"谢了啊."我没什么好谢你的.
"Hey, thank you." I have nothing to thank you for.
外面肯定出事了.
Something's going on out there.
知道吗?你就是个纵容者.
You know what? You are just an enabler.
他来了!
he's here!
行.
Okay.
行,你够狠.
Okay. You made your point.
现在咱们做笔交易,你拿着钱
Now we make a deal, and you begin
开始新生活当个有钱人,怎么样?
a new life as a wealthy man, huh?
我自己付得起账单.
I can pay my own bills.
恭喜啊.
Congrats.
- 再靠近她就死.- 不要!
- Come closer and she dies. - No!
我早料到了.
I figured that.
你该消失.拿着钱.
You should disappear. Take the money.
去过好日子.
Make a nice life.
她在哪?
Where is she?
我不认识这女人.
I do not know this woman.
你撒谎技术真烂.
You're a bad liar.
为什么要赌上一切?
Why risk everything?
为什么要为她杀这么多人?
Why kill everyone for her?
因为我承诺会罩着她.
'Cause I told her I had her back.
如果我把这女人交给你,
If I give you this woman,
你能留我活口?
you let me live?
要是我直接给你地址,
Because if I just give you the address,
你会毙了我吧?
then you shoot me, huh?
要是你给我假地址而我毙了你呢?
What if you give me a fake address and I shoot you?
这样对谁都没好处
That's bad for both of us.
沿57号公路往南开
Head south on 57.
我就把她的地址给你
Then I give you her address.
走吧
Let's go.
认识这货?
You know this guy?
当然认识 他是蝰蛇
Of course, I know. He's Viper.
人力资源部总监
He's Chief of Human Resource Department
专门负责特殊项目招募
and recruiting for special projects.
你为一个婊子做这么多?
Why you do all this for a whore?
你再说一遍
Say it again.
来 再说一次试试
Please, say that again.
怂了吧
Thought so.
好了迪米
Okay, Dimi,
告诉我咱们要去哪
tell me where we're going.
人在哪?
Where is she?
那儿
There.
她在那里面?
She's in there?
就在那儿
She's there.
说话算话?
Promise?
我保证
I promise.
她就在那儿
She's there.
为什么是她?
Why her?
谁决定的?
Who decides?
蝰蛇会去夜店
Viper goes to club,
物色漂亮妹子
takes pictures of pretty girls.
我把它们发给客户,他们自己选.
I send them to clients, they make choice.
见面已经安排好了.
Meeting is arranged.
这就是我的拿手好戏.
This is my specialty service.
就像给车配一套雪地胎.
Like shopping for a set of snow tires.
这些都是活生生的人.
These are human beings.
你他妈在开玩笑吧？
You must be kidding.
你以为钱会care
You think money gives a shit
它从哪来的?
where it comes from?
要是我不干,
If I didn't do this,
也会有别人来干.
somebody else would.
你还是没告诉我为什么.
You still haven't told me why.
你他妈为什么要追我们?
Why do you hunt us?
你有个女儿?
You have a daughter?
没有.
No.
那你就不会懂了.
Then you won't understand.
嘿,看好点.
Hey, good lookin' out.
嘿,兄弟,我们还好吗?
Hey, yo, we good, brother?
兄弟,我们离「还好」还差得远呢.
Man, we far from good.
我们跟迪米勾搭上的那个王八蛋
That motherfucker we hooked up with Dimi
今晚干掉了六个俄罗斯佬.
clapped out half a dozen Russians tonight.
听说,他现在正往迪米的陷阱屋赶.
Rumor is, he's on his way to Dimi's trap house right now.
所有人,
Everybody,
操,给我上车!
mount the fuck up!
你听到了,上车!
You heard the man. Mount up!
这真是个笑话.
That's funny shit.
这主意听着真棒啊,大小姐
Sounds lovely, Princess.
虽然我不赞成这种行为
I don't condone this behavior,
但我的银行账户举双手赞成
but my bank account does.
嘿,到点了
Hey. It's time.
咱们还他妈在这磨蹭啥?赶紧的！
What the fuck are we still doing here? Come on.
行,我去抓那个变态
Yeah. I'll get the pervert.
小子,咱们都是棋盘上的棋子,别往心里去
We're all just numbers, kid. Nothin' personal.
可老子怎么觉得这他妈就是冲我来的
Feels pretty fuckin' personal to me.
长官,咱们必须马上撤离
We have to go now, sir.
凭什么?
Why?
机不可失时不再来
It's now or never.
那就现在动手
Then it's now.
我到底怎么得罪你了?
What have I done to you?
没得罪
Nothing.
这才是最妙的地方
That's the best part.
我很好奇你身体里面...
I wonder what you look like on...
长什么样
the inside.
刚才那是什么鬼动静?
The fuck was that?
卧槽
whoa.
莱文!
Levon!
他们是在开枪吗?
Are they fucking shooting?
现在该轮到谁倒霉了,嗯?
Who's gonna get fucked now, huh?
他就在里面
He's in there.
正在血洗整个场子
Shooting the place up.
全体注意
Everybody,
锁死目标,装弹上膛.
lock and load.
我们去抓这个王八蛋.
Let's go get this motherfucker.
对,你们两个跟上我.
Yeah, you two on me.
你听到了,走吧.
You heard the man. Come on.
紧跟着,别出错.
Stay tight, stay right.
恶魔,穿过玻璃.
Demon, put it through the glass.
明白.
You got it.
莱文!
Levon!
操,闭嘴!
Shut the fuck up!
嘿,没事的.
Hey. It's gonna be okay.
是吗?
Yeah?
你只是……对.
You just... Yeah.
我开始觉得
I'm beginning to think
你他妈根本不知道自己在干什么!
that you do not know what you are doing!
别担心,先生.
Don't worry, sir.
一切都在掌控中.
Everything's under control.
我向你保证.
I promise you.
我要挖出你的心.
I'm gonna cut your heart out.
祝你好运.
Good luck.
你的真实名字是什么?
What the fuck is your real name?
莱文.
Levon.
很高兴见到你,莱文.
Nice to meet you, Levon.
你准备好了吗,孩子?
You ready, son?
我随时准备好了.
I'm always ready.
我的战斗不是为了你.
My fight wasn't with you.
我知道,兄弟.
I know, brother.
结束这一切.
Finish it.
对不起,兄弟.
Sorry, brother.
- 莱文！- 操！
- Levon! - What the fuck?
你他妈怎么敢进来?
How dare you come in here?
- 操!去你妈的!- 哦,操!
- Fuck! Shit! - Oh, fuck!
哦,这可不太好.
Oh, that is not good.
你他妈在说什么?
What the fuck?
- 等等.- 装弹!
- Hang on. - Reload!
等等,等等,等等.
wait, wait, wait.
不,不,不!
No, no, no!
- 我可以解释一切!- 操!
- I can explain everything! - Fuck!
不!
No!
哦,去你妈的.
Oh, shit.
妈妈!
Mommy!
操!
Fuck!
操蛋的婊子!
Fuckin' bitch!
操.
Fuck.
操你!
Fuck you!
现在一切都结束了.
It's over now.
去你妈的,婊子!
Fucking die, bitch!
我想我杀了她.
I think I killed her.
很好.
Good.
操.
Fuck.
卧槽
Whoa.
跟紧我背后
Stay on my six.
啥意思?
What's that mean?
跟着我
Follow me.
里面有持枪暴徒
There's an active shooter in there.
操
Shit.
弄死这孙子
Let's kill this guy.
刚才那动静?
What was that?
蓝牙耳机
Bluetooth.
那是个手雷?
Is that a grenade?
捂好耳朵
Mind your ears.
哦
Oh.
准备好了吗?
You ready?
没
No.
该撤了
Time to go.
黄泉路上见
See you on the other side.
刚才那是什么?
What was that?
给老战友的体面
Respect for an old friend.
想回家了吗?
You ready to go home?
赶紧带我离开这鬼地方
Get me the hell outta here.
好嘞兄弟
Yes, my brother.
他跑了...
He escaped...
带着那姑娘
with the girl.
这些都不是生意往来
None of this was business.
恶魔已经得手了
The devil has what he came for.
让他走
Let him go.
我明白咱们需要低调行事
I understand our need to move quietly in the world.
但我绝不会对杀害我孩子的人
But I will not turn the other cheek
忍气吞声
to the man who killed my children.
那我们就杀了你
Then we will kill you.
兄弟会的利益高于你的私人恩怨
The Brotherhood comes before your personal vengeance.
明白吗?
Do you understand?
明白
I understand.
听着...
Hey...
二五仔没好下场
snitches get stitches.
闺女! 天啊
¡Mija! Oh, my God.
- 对不起 真的对不起 - 不 别这样
- I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. - No. No.
别 别这样
No. No.
莱文!
Levon!
谢谢 太感谢了 真的谢谢你
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
我本来打算带梅丽
I was thinking about taking Merry
去鸡舍看看
out to the chicken coop today.
哦
Oh.
- 想一起去吗? - 想
- Yeah, would you like that? - Yeah.
- 好啊 - 不知道呢
- Yeah. - I don't know.
当心那只脾气暴躁的老公鸡
You better watch out for that old grumpy one.
它可凶了 超凶的
He's mean. He's mean.
真的 特别凶
Oh, no. He's mean.
爸是你!你回来了
Hey, Dad, it's you! You came back.
说过会回来的
Told you I would.
爸爸你没事吧?
You're okay, Daddy?
没事 刮胡子蹭破点皮
Yeah. I nicked myself shaving.
嗨
Hi.
欢迎回来
Welcome back.
乔伊斯
Hey, Joyce.
全须全尾回来了
You're in one piece.
勉强算吧
Just about.
看来他们没要你命啊?
Well, I guess they didn't kill you, huh?
是啊 他们可没少使劲
Nah. They really tried their best.
哦
Oh.
找到那姑娘了?
You found that girl?
找到了
I found her.
说说 我错过了什么?
So, what did I miss?
我交了个乌鸦朋友还有猫头鹰伙伴
Well, I made friends with a crow and an owl.
还有只山羊会叫我的名字了
And there's a goat I taught to say my name.
- 骗人 - 真的
- No. - Yeah.
超酷的 我就一直跟它说话
It was really cool. I was just talking,
然后它就"梅丽!
and then it was like, "Merry!
梅丽!"
"Merry!"
欢迎回家 兄弟
Welcome back, brother.
到家了
You're home.